Unbelievable! It's been half an hour.
真是令人難以置信,已過了半個小時
If this was a cartoon, you'd look like a ham now.
如果這是卡通 你應該看起來像火腿一樣
-There's the waitress. Hello,miss! -It's Phoebe!
-女侍在那兒,抱歉,小姐…等等 -是菲比!
-Okay,will that be all? -Wait. What are you doing here?
-好的,這些就是全部啦? -等等,你來這兒幹什麼?
I was over there. Then you said, "Hello,miss." So I'm here.
我本來在那兒,然後你叫 「嗨,小姐.」所以我就過來了
No,how come you're working here?
不,你怎麼會在這兒工作?
Because it's close to where I live, and the aprons are cute.
因為這兒離我的住處很近 而且圍裙也很漂亮
-Can we start over? -Okay,I'm gonna be over here.
-可以重來嗎? -好的,我到那邊去
The One With Two Parts - Part l
六人行 第1季 第16集 第17集 雙胞胎兩部曲
-=BT之家DRM小組 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 榮譽出品 河馬根據網絡字幕微調製作
I don't know whether he's testing me...
我不知道它是不是在考驗我
... but my monkey is out of control!
我的猴子已失去控制
He keeps erasing the messages on my machine.
它不斷清除我答錄機上的留言
Supposedly by accident.
應該是個意外
Oh,yeah,I've done that.
哦,是的,我做過這種事
And then he got to the newspaper before I did...
它連續三天在我看報紙前
...and peed all over the crossword!
在猜字遊戲上尿尿
I've never done that.
這我沒做過
Last night,I don't know what he did but there were capers everywhere!
昨晚,我不知道他做了什麼 他到處蹦來蹦去!
-She looks exactly like her sister. -I'm saying I see a difference.
-她看起來和她姐姐完全一樣 -我看到不同之處
They're twins.
她們是雙胞胎
I don't care. Phoebe's Phoebe. Ursula's hot!
我不管,菲比是菲比,烏蘇拉很火辣
You know how we talk about things?
你知道我們怎麼說這種事情?
-Let's not do that anymore. -All right.
-別再談論那事了 -好吧
-Pheebs,guess who we saw today? -Oh,fun! Okay.
-菲比,猜我們今天遇見誰? -哦,好玩的事情!好的
-Liam Neeson. -No.
-連恩尼遜 -不是
-Morley Safer. -No.
-茉莉.塞弗 -不是
-The lady who cuts my hair! -This could be a very long game.
-剪我頭髮的女人! -這會是一個很長的遊戲
-Your sister,Ursula. -Oh,really?
-你姐姐,烏蘇拉 -哦,真的?
-She works at that place.... -Riff's. I know.
-她在那兒工作… -瑞菲餐廳,我知道
You do? She said you guys haven't talked in years.
你知道?因為她說你們已多年不說話
So,is she fat?
對,她胖嗎?
Not from where I was standing.
從我的角度看不會
Where were you standing?
你從什麼角度?
Pheebs,so you guys just don't get along?
菲比,你們合不來?
It's mostly just dumb sister stuff.
這只是姐妹之間的事
Everyone always thought of her as the pretty one.
大家都認為她漂亮
She was the first to walk even though I did it later that same day.
她先學會走路 雖然我是在當天稍後學會的
But to my parents,by then it was, "Yeah,what else is new?"
對我爸媽而言那,就已經不新鮮了
I'm sorry. I've gotta go. I've got Lamaze class.
菲比,抱歉,我得走了 我得去參加心理助產班
And I've got earth science, but I'll catch you in gym?
我得去參加地球科學班 健身房見了
-ls this just gonna be you and Carol? -Susan will be there too.
-就你和卡蘿兩人去? -不,蘇珊也要去
We've got dads,we've got lesbians. The whole parenting team.
那有爸爸,女同志…全部的父母都會到
-lsn't that gonna be weird? -lt might have been at first...
-這樣不是會很奇怪? -不會的,一開始或許會
... but now I'm comfortable with it.
現在我已坦然面對
-Ross,that's my jacket. -I know.
-羅斯,那是我的外套 -我知道
Hi. We're the Rostens. I'm J. C. and he's Michael.
我們姓羅,我是潔西他叫麥可
And we're having a boy and a girl.
我們有一個男孩和一個女孩
Good for you. All right,next?
厲害,下一位
I'm Ross Geller. And that's my boy in there.
我叫羅斯,我兒子在那兒
And this is Carol Willick. And this is Susan Bunch.
她叫卡羅,這位是蘇珊
Susan is Carol's....
蘇珊是卡羅的…
Who's next?
下一位是誰?
Sorry,Susan is...?
抱歉,蘇珊是…
-Carol's friend. -Life partner.
-蘇珊是卡蘿的朋友 -生活拍檔
Like buddies.
就像夥伴
-Like lovers. -You know how close women can get.
-好像戀人 -你知道女人能有多親近的
-We live together. -I was married to her.
-我們倆住在一起 -我倆曾經結過婚
-Carol,not me. -It's a bit complicated.
-卡蘿,不是我 -有點複雜了
-But we're fine. -Absolutely!
-但是我們不錯 -絕對的!
So,twins! That's like two births.
雙胞胎,好像要生兩次
Ouch!
噢!
to you too,Helen.
彼此,海倫
-Nina Bookbinder is here to see you. -Okay,send her in.
-妮娜.布克賓德來找你 -好的,讓她進來
-Come on in. -You wanted to see me?
-妮娜,快進來 -你想見我?
I was reviewing your data. You've been postdating your Friday numbers.
我剛看過你的資料 你一直填遲你週五數字的日期
-Which is bad,because...? -lt throws my WENUS out of whack.
-這樣很不好,因為… -這樣使我的WEENUS出現問題
-Excuse me? -WENUS.
-對不起? -WEENUS…
Weekly Estimated Net Usage Statistics.
「Weekly Estimated Net Usage Statistics」 每週估計淨值使用統計
Gotcha!
對
Won't happen again. I wouldn't want to do anything to hurt your WENUS.
不會再發生了 我不會做任何事傷害你的…維納斯(WEENUS)
I'll take "ldiots in the Workplace" for 200,Alex.
要我就在「工廠裡的白癡」上押200,亞里克斯
It's not just that she's cute,okay? It's just that...
這不是她漂不漂亮的問題,這是…
...she's really,really cute.
她真的很漂亮
It doesn't matter. You don't dip your pen in the company ink.
都一樣,兔子不吃窩邊草
God,I even know that and I'm pretty much unemployable.
上帝,我知道我幾乎不應該被僱用
Ross,your little creature's got the remote again.
羅斯你的小動物又在玩遙控器
Marcel,give Rossy the remote.
馬修,把遙控器給羅斯
Marcel!
馬修!
Marcel,you give Rossy the remote right now!
馬修,現在馬上把遙控器給羅斯
You give Rossy the remote
把遙控器給羅斯
-Great. -Relax. I'll fix it.
-這下好了 -放心.我會修好的
Oh,cool! Urkel in Spanish is Urkel.
酷在西班牙文中叫「烏酷」
How did he do this?
他是怎麼辦到的?
Is leaving Christmas lights up your plan to keep us merry all year long?
你讓聖誕燈開是想讓我們「快樂」一整年?
No,someone was supposed to take them down but obviously someone forgot.
不,某人在新年期間就應該把它拿下 她顯然是忘了
Someone was supposed to write, "Rach,take down the lights"...
某人應該寫個字條「瑞秋,拿下聖誕燈」
...and put it on the refrigera
然後貼在冰…
-How long has that been there? -A really long time.
-在這兒多久了? -時間可不短了
-Where you been? -Riff's.
-你上哪兒去了? -瑞佛餐廳
I think Ursula likes me. I ordered coffee.
我想烏蘇拉喜歡我 我只點咖啡
She brought me a tuna melt and four plates of curly fries.
她卻端給我鮪魚和四盤的薯片
Score.
有門了
She is so hot!
她好帶勁兒
Before you do anything Joey-like, you might want to run it by....
你展開「喬依」行動之前, 或許你可以找…
-Pheebs? -Yeah.
-菲比? -當然
Is it okay if I asked out your sister?
菲比,我約你姐出去你會介意嗎?
Why? Why would you want to do that? Why?
為什麼?你為何要那樣做?為什麼?
So if we went out on a date, she'd be there.
因為如果我去約會時,她就會在我身邊
Well,I'm not my sister's, you know,whatever.
好吧,不管怎樣,我不是她
And I mean,it's true, we were one egg once.
沒錯,我們確實曾待在同一顆卵子
But you know, we've grown apart so....
但我們各自發育
I don't know. Why not?
我不知道…有何不可?
Cool. Thanks.
酷.謝啦
-You okay? -Yeah,I'm fine.
-你還好吧? -還好
Do you wanna watch Laverne y Shirley?
你還要繼續看?
Sorry.
抱歉
Hi. Sorry I'm late. Where's Carol?
抱歉,我遲到了.卡蘿在哪兒?
Stuck at school. Some parent-teacher thing.
學校有事,老師和家長間的事
You can go. I'll get the information.
你可以走了,我留下來上課
No,I think I should stay. We should both know what's going on.
不…我應該留下來 我們兩個都該留下來上課
Oh,good. This will be fun.
很好,一定會很有意思的
We're gonna start with some basic third-stage breathing exercises.
首先是第三階段基本呼吸練習
Moms,get on your back.
各位媽媽請躺下
And coaches,you should be supporting Mommy's head.
教練們支撐媽媽們的頭
-What? -What?
-什麼? -什麼?
-I'm supposed to be the mommy? -I'll play my sperm card once more.
-我該當媽? -好吧,我再打一次精子牌
I have to miss the coaching training because I'm a woman?
只因我是個女人 我就得錯過教練訓練
-So,what do we do? -I'll flip you for it.
-瞭解,你說該怎麼辦? -擲銅板
Flip me for it? No,no. Heads!
擲銅板?不…我選頭…
On your back,Mom!
躺下吧,媽
All right,mommies,take a nice deep,cleansing breath.
各位媽媽們,請深呼吸
Good.
很好
Now imagine your vagina is opening like a flower.
很好,現在請想像你的陰道 像花一樣綻放著
-Mr. D! How's it going,sir? -It's been better.
-迪先生,如何? -好多了
The Annual Net Usage Statistics are in.
年度淨值已經算出來了
-And? -It's pretty ugly.
-然後呢? -奇慘無此
We haven't seen an ANUS this bad since the '70s.
70年代之後沒見過這麼慘的ANUS
-What does this mean? -We'll be laying off people.
-這代表什麼? -每個部門都得裁員
I know I was late last week. But I slept funny and
我知道雖然我上星期遲到, 我那天睡姿不良把頭髮睡塌?
Not you. Relax.
不是你,放鬆
Ever have to fire anyone?
曾經必須開除某人嗎?
No,but that's not a problem. That's why my name's on the door.
沒有,不過那不成問題. 這就是我的名字在門上的原因啊
Do you know when I'm getting my name on the door?
你知道我什麼時候,能在門上有自己的名字嗎?
I don't know. I put it in the thing.
我不清楚.我會記下來的
It's okay. So,who is it gonna be?
不說這些.那將會是誰呢?
Nina!
妮娜!
Nina.
妮娜
Are you okay?
你沒事吧?
Yes. Yes,I am.
是的,我沒事
Listen,the reason that I called you in here today was....
聽著,我今天叫你進來…是因為
Please don't hate me.
請別恨我
What?
怎麼了?
Would you like to have dinner sometime?
能約你共進晚餐嗎?
So,what do you want for your birthday?
菲比,你想要什麼生日禮物?
What I want is for my mom to be alive and enjoy it with me.
我想要我媽復活和我共享人生
Okay. Let me put it this way. Anything from Crabtree & Evelyn?
好吧.這樣吧.想不想要「艾芙琳」的產品?
-Bath salts would be nice! -Okay! Good.
-我想要浴鹽! -好的!
What is this place?
這是什麼地方?
You're cold,I have to pee and there's coffee. How bad could it be?
你很冷,我想尿尿, 窗戶上有個咖啡杯 還有比這更糟的嗎?
I think we have an answer.
我想我們有答案了
Why is she here?
她怎麼會在這兒?
This could be God's way of telling us to eat at home.
也許這就是老天爺叫我們回家吃飯的方法
-Think Riff's fired her? -No,we were there last night.
-她被瑞佛餐廳開除? -不,昨晚我們還在那兒吃飯,她不斷端來劍魚
Are you gonna go to the...?
你不是要去…?
-I'll wait till we order. It's her. -lt looks like her.
-不,點完之後再去 -是她吧?看起來像她
-Excuse me? -Yeah.
-抱歉? -是
Hi,it's us!
是我們
Right. And it's me!
好呀,是我
-So you're here too? -As much as you are.
-你也在這兒? -和你們一樣
Your turn.
該你了
-We know what we want. -That's good.
-我們知道我們要什麼 -很好
-Two caffe lattes. -And some biscotti.
我們要兩杯拿鐵還有小餅乾
Good choice.
不錯的選擇
-It's definitely her. -Yeah.
-絕對是她 -絕對是她
I can't believe you haven't told that girl she doesn't have a job.
我真不敢相信, 你還沒告訴她她失業了?
You haven't taken down the Christmas lights.
你還沒把聖誕燈拿下來
Congratulations! You've found the world's thinnest argument.
恭喜!你發現了世上最薄弱的論點
I'm finding the right moment.
我只是在尋找適當的時機
That shouldn't be so hard now that you're dating.
應該不會太難找到 因為你們已開始約會
"Honey,you're fired. But how about a quickie before I go to work?"
親愛的,你被開除了 我上班前何不來個「速戰速決」
Once you're inside, you don't have to knock anymore.
進門後就不用再敲門了
I'll get it.
我來開
-Hi,Mr. Heckles. -You're doing it again.
-哈克先生 -你們又來了
We're not doing anything. We're sitting and talking quietly.
我們什麼都沒做. 我們只是坐在這兒靜靜地聊天
I can hear you through the ceiling.
我可以透過天花板聽見
My cats can't sleep.
我的貓睡不著
-You don't even have cats. -I could have cats.
-你根本沒養貓 -我原本有機會養
-Goodbye,Mr. Heckles. -We'll try to keep it down.
-再見了,哈先生 -我們會很小聲的
Phoebe,do me a favor. Try this on. I want to make sure it fits.
菲比,幫個忙,能試穿看看嗎? 我想知道合不合身?
My first birthday present! This is really
我的第一件生日禮物,這衣服真…
No,no,it's for Ursula. I just figured size-wise....
不,是送烏蘇拉的,我只是想知道尺寸
Sure. Yeah. Okay,it fits.
好呀,合身
-Are you seeing her again? -Yep,lce Capades.
-你今晚又和她約會? -對,去看花樣滑冰
This is serious. I've never known you to pay for any kind of "capade."
這回你是來真的 沒想到你會為任何花式玩意兒付錢
I don't know. I like her.
我也不知道,我喜歡她
She's different. There's something about her
她與眾不同,她有…
That you like. We get it. You like her. Great!
你喜歡?我們懂 你喜歡她,太好了
Phoebe,I asked you. You said it was okay.
菲比,我問過你而你也同意了
Maybe now it's not okay.
也許現在不同意了
Okay. Maybe now I'm not okay with it not being okay.
也許我對於你的不同意也不同意了
Okay!
好吧!
IKnit,good woman,knit!
快織,好女人
And that's the Chrysler Building right there.
克萊斯勒大樓就在那兒
-Nina! -Mr. Douglas. Cool tie.
-妮娜! -道格拉斯先生.領帶不錯
She's still here.
她還在這裡?
Yes. Yes,she is. Didn't I memo you on this?
沒錯,她還在.我沒有給你這個備忘錄嗎?
After I let her go,I got a call from her psychiatrist,Dr. Flennan
我開除她後,接到她心理醫生的電話
Dr. Flennan Dr. Flynn.
佛…佛林大夫
And he informed me that she took the news rather badly.
他說她一時無法適應
In fact,he mentioned the word "frenzy."
老實說他提到「狂暴」這兩個字
-You're kidding! She seems so -No. Nina? She's
-她?開什麼玩笑?她…  -不,妮娜?她…
If you asked her now...
如果你現在問她
...she'd have no recollection of being fired at all.
她根本記不得被開除這件事
-That's unbelievable. -And yet believable.
-難以置信 -你不得不信
So I decided not to fire her again until she'll be no threat to anyone.
因此我決定暫時不再開除她 直到我確定她對自己或其他人不構成威脅為止
I guess you never know what's going on inside a person's head.
人的心中在想什麼 別人永遠無法完全瞭解
Well,I guess that's why they call it psychology,sir.
我想這就是為什麼被成為「心理學」了
The sound Mom and Dad will never forget.
爸媽永遠忘不了這聲音
For this,after all, is the miracle of birth.
這個,畢竟是生產的奇跡
Lights,please. And that's having a baby.
請開燈,這一集是生寶寶
Next week is our final class.
下周是我們的最後一堂課
Susan,go deep.
蘇珊,準備接球
-It's just impossible. -What is,honey?
-這太離譜了… -怎麼了?
What that woman did.
那個女人幹了什麼
I am not doing that. It'll just have to stay in.
我不會這麼做的.他得留在我體內
Everything will be the same. It'll just stay in.
一切和原來一樣,他得留在我體內
-Carol,honey,it'll be all right. -What do you know?
-卡蘿,親愛的,不會有事的 -你怎麼知道?
No one's asking you,"Mind if we push this pot roast through your nostril?"
你怎麼知道?沒人問你,我能將這肉塊穿你的鼻孔嗎?
Carol,sweetie. Cleansing breath.
卡蘿,親愛的,深呼吸
I know it's frightening. But big picture:
我知道你很惶恐,往遠處想
The birth part is just one day.
生產過程只是一天
When it's over,we'll all be parents for the rest of our lives.
結束後我們這輩子都是他的父母了
I mean,that's what this is all about,right? Ross?
懷胎生子為的不就是這些嗎?羅斯?
Ross?
羅斯?
I'm gonna be a father.
我要當爸爸了
-This is news to you? -I knew I was having a baby.
-你才剛知道? -我一直都知道我有個孩子
I just never realized the baby was having me.
只是不知道孩子有我
-You'll be great. -How can you say that?
-你會是個好爸爸的 -你怎會知道?
I can't even get Marcel to stop eating the bathmat.
我連阻止馬修吃浴室墊都辦不到
-How will I raise a kid? -Some scientists are now saying...
-我如何養兒育女? -羅斯,科學家說
...that monkeys and babies are actually different.
孩子和猴子是不一樣的
You might want to look into it.
我們可以驗證一下
-Where you going? -Out.
-你去哪裡? -外面
With...?
和誰?
Yes.
是的
Can I just ask you one question?
能問你一個問題嗎?
Have you two,you know, like,you know?
你們有沒有,你明白的,就像,你知道的嘛?
You know,yet?
你知道的,對吧?
Not that it's any of your business, but no,we haven't.
不關你的事,沒有,行了嗎?
You meant sex,right?
你是指性吧?
-Do you have a sec? -Sure. What's up?
-有空嗎? -當然,什麼事?
The past few days,people have been avoiding me and giving me weird looks.
最近幾天,大家都避開我 而且以奇怪的眼神看我
Well,maybe that's because they're jealous of us.
或許他們在嫉妒我們
Maybe. But that doesn't explain why they keep taking my scissors.
或許吧,這無法解釋他們為何拿走我的剪刀
Maybe that's because you're getting a big raise!
或許是因為你被升職的緣故
-I am? -Sure. Why not?
-我升職了? -當然.為什麼不呢?
Oh,my God! You're amazing!
天啊,你真是太了不起了
You don't know.
你不知道
Helen,do the paperwork on Miss Bookbinder's raise.
海倫,能快處理布小姐升職的手續嗎?
You still want me to send her psychological profile to Personnel?
你仍要我拿她的心理分析結果到人事部?
Helen drinks.
海倫喝醉了
Will you marry me?
你願意嫁給我嗎?
So after the proposal, I kind of unraveled.
升職後的事情,我就未經修剪了
Right. Because you were really in control up until then.
是啊.因為你控制全盤直到那個時候
-I told her everything. -How'd she take it?
-最後我把一切都告訴她了 -她的反應如何?
Pretty well. Except for the stapler thing.
坦然接受,除了拿釘書機釘我之外
A tip. If you're ever in a similar situation...
提示.以後遇見類似的狀況
... never,ever leave your hand on the desk.
切記別把手放在桌上
Okay,I think I get how to do this.
我知道該怎麼調成這樣了啊
Can we turn it off? Make them go away because I can't watch.
我們能把這關掉嗎? 把他們弄走,因為我沒法看了啊
Okay,they're gone.
好了,現在沒有了
Are you all right?
你還好吧?
It's just this whole stupid Ursula thing.
還不是烏蘇拉惹的禍
Pheebs,can I ask? So he's going out with her. Is it really so terrible?
菲比,我能問… 他和她約會真有那麼糟嗎?
Yeah.
是的
I'm not saying she's evil or anything.
我不是說她是很壞
She's just always breaking my stuff.
她總是弄壞我的東西
When I was 8,she threw my Judy Jetson Thermos under the bus.
我8歲時,她把我得朱迪傑特森 熱水壺丟到公車下
And then when I was 1 2, she broke my collarbone.
我12歲的時候,她弄斷了我的鎖骨
She didn't mean to do it but I think it still counts.
她不是有意的,不過也算
And then there's Randy Brown, who was like
然後,有個藍迪布朗,就像
Have you ever had a boyfriend who was your best friend?
你們有沒有過男友身兼好友的情況?
That's what he was for me.
我當時的狀況就是如此
And she kind of stole him away and then broke his heart.
她把他搶走又傷了他的心
Then he wouldn't talk to me anymore.
他從此不和我說話
He didn't want to be around anything that looked like either one of us.
因為他說他不願再見像她的人
I know Joey's not my boyfriend or my thermos...
我知道喬伊不是我男朋友或者熱水壺
...or anything,but
或其他的什麼,但是
-You won't lose him. -You gotta talk to Joey.
-你不會失去他的 -你得找喬伊談
-lf he knew how you felt -But he's falling in love with her.
-如果他知道你的感受 -但他愛上她了
They've been going out a week.
拜託,他們才約會一個星期
They haven't even slept together yet. That's not serious.
根本還沒上床八字都還沒一撇呢
Okay. Okay.
好吧.好吧
May we help you?
需要幫忙嗎?
What are you doing? It's freezing! Come inside.
瑞秋,你在幹什麼?外面好冷,進來好嗎?
No,you wanted me to take them down...
不…你要我把燈取下
...so I'm taking them down,okay?
我正在做,行嗎?
Rachel!
天啊,瑞秋!
I'm okay. I'm okay.
我沒事…
Mr. Heckles?
哈克先生…
Mr. Heckles,could you help me,please?
哈克先生…能幫一下忙嗎?
This is just the kind of thing I was talking about.
我指的就是這種事兒
My friend was taking down Christmas lights...
我朋友取下聖誕燈時
...and may have broken her ankle.
從陽台跌下來,可能傷了腳踝
My God,you still have your Christmas lights up?
你們的聖誕燈還亮著?
-Fill this out and bring it back. -Here you go.
-填好資料後拿給我 -給你
All right. Name,address.
姓名?地址
-Are you currently on any medication? -No.
-你現在進行任何藥物治療? -沒有
Oh,wait! Yes. Blistex.
哦,等等!有.Blistex（一種藥用潤唇膏）
-No. In case of emergency,call...? -You.
-填沒有，緊急聯絡電話? -你
-Really? -Yeah.
-真的? -對
Oh,that is so sweet!
你真好
Gosh,love you. Okay,insurance?
我愛你.保險?
Oh,yeah,check it. Definitely gonna want some of that!
哦,打勾,我當然需要保險
-You don't have insurance? -How much will this cost?
-你沒有保險? -要多少錢?
X-rays alone could be $200!
單是X光就可能得要好兩百元
-What are we gonna do? -There's not much we can do.
-我們該怎麼辦? -沒有太多辦法可想
Unless I use yours.
除非我用你的
-No,no,no. -Now wait a second.
-不,不,不 -等等
Who did I just put as my emergency person?
我的緊急連絡人是誰?
That's insurance fraud.
這是保險欺詐
All right then,forget it. Might as well just go home.
好吧.算了.我回家
-Okay,come here. I hate this. -Thank you. I love you.
-好吧,回來,我真討厭這樣做 -謝謝?我愛你
Hi. I'm gonna need a new set of these forms.
我需要新表格
-Why? -I am really an idiot.
-為什麼? -我真是個笨蛋
I was filling out her form...
我替我朋友填資料時
...and instead of putting her information I put mine.
填的不是她的資料而是我的
You are an idiot.
你真是個笨蛋
Yep,that's me. I am that stupid.
沒錯?這就是我.我就是那麼笨
I had a dream. I was playing football with my kid.
我夢見我和我兒子在玩橄欖球
-That's nice. -No,no. With him.
-真溫馨 -不?他是球
I'm on this field, and they hike me the baby.
我在球場上,他們叫我以兒子做襠下開球
I've gotta do something. The Tampa Bay defense is coming right at me!
我得做點什麼,坦帕灣隊的防守球員逐漸逼近
-Tampa Bay's got a terrible team. -Right,but...
-坦帕灣隊爛得可怕 -沒錯?
...it is just me and the baby, so I'm thinking they can take us.
但只有我和我兒子.我想我們死定了
And so I just heave it downfield!
所以我只好傳球
-What are you,crazy? That's a baby! -He should take the sack?
-什麼?你瘋啦?他是你兒子 -他該擒抱?
Anyway,suddenly I'm downfield.
總之,突然我又到了前場
And I realize I'm the one who's supposed to catch him.
我發現該接球的人是我
I know I'm not gonna get there in time.
但我絕對來不及
So I am running and running. That is when I woke up.
於是我跑啊跑,然後就驚醒了
See? I am so not ready to be a father.
看?我還沒準備好當爸爸
You're gonna be fine.
你沒問題的
You're one of the most caring, responsible men in North America.
你是全美最細心,最有責任感的男人
You're gonna make a great dad.
你將來一定是個好爸爸的
Yeah,you and the baby just need better blocking.
沒錯?你和你兒子,只是需要更好的阻擋
Have you ever been to the Rainbow Room? Is it expensive?
你們去過彩虹廳嗎?真有那麼貴?
Well,only if you order stuff.
當然,只有你去才會貴
I'm taking Ursula tonight. It's her birthday.
我今晚要帶烏蘇拉去,今天是她生日
-What about Phoebe's birthday? -When's that?
-菲比的生日該怎麼辦? -什麼時候?
-Tonight. -What are the odds of that happening?
-今晚 -怎麼會有這麼巧的事情發生呢?
You take your time.
慢慢想吧
There it is!
原來是這樣啊!
-What'll you do? -What can I do?
-你打算怎麼辦? -我能怎麼辦?
I don't wanna screw it up with Ursula.
我不想讓烏蘇拉不開心
And your friend?
你的朋友菲比呢?
If she's my friend,she'll understand. Wouldn't you?
如果她是我朋友希望她能諒解. 你們能諒解嗎?
If you tried that on my birthday...
我生日時如果你敢這樣做
...you'd be staring at the end of a hissy fit.
我就和你沒完沒了
Saffron makes all the difference.
加上少量蕃紅花,就能使情況完全改觀
-Okay. Monica? -Yes.
-摩妮卡? -是…
-Yes,she is. -Hi,this is my friend Rachel.
-是…她 -她是我朋友瑞秋
-Hi,I'm Dr. Mitchell. -And I'm Dr. Rosen.
-瑞秋?我是米契爾大夫 -我是羅森大夫
I'm okay here.
我在這沒問題
Actually,that's all right. You can take your break.
好吧,就這樣.你可以休息一下
No,this is why I became a doctor. Ankles and stuff like that.
不了,這就是我為什麼做了一聲. 腳踝之類是我得專長啊
-Aren't you too cute to be a doctor? -Excuse me?
-你當醫生是否太帥了一點? -抱歉?
God,young,young. I meant young. Young to be a doctor. Good,Rach.
天哪,年輕,我是指年輕 你當醫生稍嫌年輕了點,說得好,瑞秋
-Thank you. -Right.
-謝謝 -好的
He said it was just a sprain.
他說這只是扭傷
-You left out the stupid part. -It's not stupid.
-你忘了說我們做的蠢事 -才不蠢呢
The cute doctors asked us out for tomorrow,and I said yes.
這位兩位帥哥大夫約我們明晚出去, 我答應了
I think it's insane. They work for the hospital.
你根本就是瘋了,他們在醫院工作
It's like returning to the scene of the crime.
我們這樣不是回到犯罪現場?
-I say we blow off the dates. -What? They are cute.
-還是取消約會吧 -什麼?他們可是大帥哥
They are doctors. Cute doctors. Doctors who are cute.
而且還是醫生.帥哥醫生?很帥的醫生
All right,what have we learned so far?
目前為止我們學習到什麼?
Oh,God. Okay.
天啊
Surprise!
驚喜
What are you doing? You scared the crap out of me!
你們在幹什麼?把我嚇死了!
-Was that the cake? -Yeah. I got a lemon schmoosh.
-那是蛋糕嗎? -對?檸檬口味
Come on. She'll be here any minute.
快?她隨時會到
Hope it's okay.
希望蛋糕沒事
"Happy Birthday Peehee."
「生日快樂?菲…」
Maybe we can make a "B" out of a rose.
或許我們可以用玫瑰當「比」
We'll just use our special cake tools.
對?用我們的特殊蛋糕工具
-What's going on? -We just
-什麼事? -我們只是
Surprise!
驚喜!
This is so great! Oh,my God! This was not at all scary.
你們真是太好了,一點都不嚇人
Look! "Happy Birthday Peehee."
看哪!「生日快樂,菲」
What a strange new nickname. I like it! Oh,my God!
好奇怪得暱稱啊.我好喜歡,哦上帝!
Hi,everybody. Hi,Betty! Betty,hi!
各位?貝蒂!貝蒂!
You found Betty! Oh,my gosh! This is so great.
你找到貝蒂?太好了
Everybody I love is in the same room. Where's Joey?
我愛的大家都同在一起,喬伊在哪兒?
Did you see Betty?
你看見貝蒂沒?
I wouldn't mind having a piece of this sun-dried tomato business.
蕃茄幹事業真好賺
Five years ago,if somebody had said, "A tomato that's like a prune"...
五年前如果有人說我的蕃茄像李子
... I'd have said,"Get out!"
我就叫他滾出我的辦公室
Dad,before I was born, did you freak out?
爸?我出生前你會緊張嗎?
I'm not freaking out! I'm saying, if someone had come to me
我不緊張,我是說如果有人對我說…
Dad,I'm talking about the whole baby thing.
爸?我在談小孩的事
Did you ever get this sort of...
你是否曾因為
... panicky,"Oh,my God, I'm gonna be a father" thing?
將成為父親而緊張?
No. We just had kids back then.
不會.我們只是要回收種子
We didn't think about it. What else could the sun dry,I wonder?
我們根本就不想這些. 我在想除了曬乾還能怎麼辦?
Dad,come on. IKids.
老爸,不要這樣,我們在說孩子
Look,your mother really did the work. I was busy with the business.
都是你媽在處理,我忙著事業
I wasn't around that much. Is that what this is about?
經常不在家,你找我來是為了這個?
No,I was just wondering.
不是?我只是有點迷惑
We can make up for that. We can do stuff together.
因為我們有時間彌補 我們可以一起做某些事
You always wanted to go to Colonial Williamsburg. Let's do that.
你一直想去威廉斯堡,想去嗎?
Thanks,Dad,really. You know,I just....
謝了,爸.我只是
I just needed to know...
我只是想知道
...when did you start to feel like a father?
你何時感覺自己像個父親
Well,I guess it must've been the day after you were born.
應該是你出生那一天
We were in the hospital room, your mom was asleep...
我們在病房,你媽在睡覺
...and they brought you in and gave you to me.
他們把你交給我
You were this ugly little red thing.
你當時又醜又紅又小
All of a sudden you grabbed my finger with your fist...
你突然用拳頭緊抓住我的手指
...and you squeezed it so tight.
緊緊捏住我的手指
And that's when I knew.
那時候我才感覺到
So you don't wanna go to Williamsburg?
你不想去威廉斯堡?
We can go to Williamsburg.
我們可以去阿
Eat your fish.
吃魚吧
-Rachel,the cute doctors are here! -Okay,coming.
-瑞秋?帥哥醫生來了! -來了
-Hi,come on in. -Hi,Jeffrey.
-請進 -你好,麥可.傑佛瑞
We brought wine.
我們帶了一瓶酒
Look. It's from the cellars of Ernest and Tova Borgnine.
這是來自恩尼斯及托夫波尼酒窖
-How could we resist? -That's great!
-我們怎麼能夠拒絕呢? -太好了!
-Monica,how's the ankle? -It's....
-摩妮卡,腳踝如何? -它啊
Why don't you tell them? After all,it is your ankle.
你何不告訴他們,這可是你的腳踝
It's feeling a lot better. Thank you.
感覺好多了,謝謝
Why don't you guys sit down, and we'll get you some glasses?
你們請坐我去拿杯子
Okay. Stat!
快坐好
Why don't we just tell them who we really are? It'll be fine.
我們何不表明我們的身份 絕對不會有事的
-We'll get in trouble. -Would you stop being such a wuss?
-我們會惹上大麻煩 -摩妮卡,別那麼不爭氣
A wuss? Excuse me for living in the real world.
不爭氣?抱歉,我生在真實的世界之中
-So? -So they still seem normal.
所以呢?她們似乎很正常
Because they are.
但你得承認
When we go out with women from the hospital
每次我們和女病患約會都…
Relax. Take a look around. There are no pagan altars.
別緊張,看看四周.沒有異教徒的神壇
No piles of bones in the corners. They're fine. Go like this:
角落沒有成堆的骨頭, 她們沒事的,這個…
We're not going to do it. Sometimes you can be such a baby!
我們絕不能這麼做,有時你真的很幼稚
-I am not a baby. -Be serious. Every time
-我才不幼稚 -嚴格來說,每次都是
-You act like a princess. -You know what?
-你嬌生慣養… -你知道嗎?
Every day you are becoming more and more like your mother. Excuse me.
你愈來愈像你媽了
Here we go.
來
Great place. How long have you lived here?
這房子好漂亮,住在這兒多久了?
I've been here about six years.
謝謝,我住在這兒六年了
And Rachel moved in a few months ago.
瑞秋幾個月從才搬來
See,I was supposed to get married, but I left the guy at the altar.
對,我本來應該結婚的 但我在聖堂前離開了新郎
-Really? -Yeah.
-真的? -是的
Yeah,I know it's pretty selfish, but hey,that's me!
對,我知道我很自私 但我就是這種人
-Try the hummus. -Monica,what do you do?
-試試這個鷹嘴豆沙 -摩妮卡,你從事什麼工作?
I am a chef at a restaurant uptown.
我在上城區一家餐廳的總廚師
-Good for you. -Yeah,it is.
-真有你的 -沒錯
Mostly because I get to boss people around,which I just love to do.
因為我喜歡指使別人
-This hummus is great. -God bless the chickpea.
-這個鷹嘴豆沙不錯. -上帝保佑鷹嘴豆
Oh,God! I am so spoiled!
我真是被寵壞了
That's it.
就這樣了
I shoplift.
我偷東西
You had no idea that lipstick was in your pocket.
你絕對想不到唇膏在我的口袋中
Did I tell you that I think I'm so much cuter than I am?
我告訴過你們我比原來可愛多了嗎?
And have I mentioned that back in high school I was a cow?
對了,我有提過,我在高中是條肥豬?
I used to wet my bed.
我常尿床
I use my breasts to get people's attention.
我以胸部吸引別人的注意
We both do that!
我們都一樣
Monica and Rachel's apartment.
摩妮卡與瑞秋的公寓
Just one second. Rachel,it's your dad.
等等,瑞秋,是你爸
Hi,Dad. No,no,it's me.
爸?不,是我
Listen,Dad,I can't talk right now.
聽我說,老爸,我現在沒空
But there's something....
但有些
There's something I've been meaning to tell you.
有些話我一直想告訴你
-Excuse me. -Remember back in freshman year?
失陪一下,記得我大一時嗎?
Well,Billy Dreskin and I had sex on your bed.
我和比利在你床上做愛
Daddy.
爸
Why? Why would I sleep with Billy Dreskin?
為什麼?我幹嘛和比利上床?
His father tried to put you out of business! You are dead!
他爸想害你倒閉!你死定了!
Hey,Rachel? Are these your condoms?
嗨,瑞秋?這是你的保險套嗎?
Oh,no,that was just Monica. She's drunk again.
哦,不,那是摩尼卡.她又喝醉了
I don't think "scrunchy" is a word.
我不記得「scrunchy」是一個詞
Why not,if "crunchy" is a word?
為什麼不是,「嘎吱嘎吱」都是一個詞呢?
Then I'm using that same argument for "fligament."
那這麼說「fligament」也是詞了啊
-Ross,he's got the remote again. -Good.
-羅斯,他又在玩遙控器了 -好的
Maybe he can switch it back.
或許他能將功能變回來
Maybe not.
或許不會
Okay,Daddy? That's the other line.
ok,爸爸?那是另一條線
Okay,no,not even in my bedroom.
沒有,沒有,也沒有在我的臥室裡過
Okay. Okay. Bye-bye.
ok.ok.再見
Hello?
你好?
Hold on a second. Let me check and see if she's here.
等等,我看看她在不在
It's the woman from the hospital. There's a problem.
醫院那個女人打來的,她說表格有問題
-What do we do? -Just find out what they want.
-我們該怎麼辦? -你去問他們想幹什麼
Okay. No,you do it.
不,你問
Hello. This is Monica. Yeah?
我是摩妮卡,是的?
Oh,okay. Yes,we'll be right down. Thank you.
好,我們馬上去,謝謝
We forgot to sign one of the admissions forms.
什麼事?我們忘了簽名
You were right. This was just not worth it. Let me just change.
你說得對,不值得這麼做.我們改回來
-"Garge"? -Nautical term.
-「Garge」? -航海時間
-Cheating man. -Okay.
-作弊男 -好吧
-She still didn't call? -No.
-她還沒有打電話 -沒有
Trouble?
有心事?
Your sister stood me up.
你妹放我鴿子
Don't you hate it when people aren't there for you?
被人放鴿子的滋味不好受吧
-What is that? -"Tushy."
-這是什麼? -「Tushy.」
-Did you try calling her? -For two days.
-你有打電話給她嗎? -我連打了兩天
At the restaurant they said she was busy.
打給餐廳時他們說她太忙
I can't believe she's blowing me off!
我不敢相信她想甩掉我
-We had the two chef salads. -And how were they?
-我們吃了兩份主沙拉 -我們還能怎樣?
No,we haven't had them yet. We're still hoping to have them.
不,我們還沒有吃.我們只是希望吃那個
Okay.
好吧
-You got a minute? -Yeah,I'm just working.
-有空嗎? -有,我只是在工作
So.
那…
-I got you a birthday present. -Wow,you remembered.
-我為你買了生日禮物 -嗚,你記得
-It's a Judy Jetson thermos. -Like the kind you
-是個茱蒂傑森熱水壺 -對,像你…
Right. Oh,I got something for you too.
對,我也有東西送你
-How'd you know I was coming? -Yeah,twin thing.
-你怎知道我會來? -我們是雙胞胎嘛
I can't believe you did this.
我不敢相信你會這麼做
So,what's the deal with you and Joey?
你和喬伊之間呢?
Oh,right. He is so great. But that's over.
他人很好,但我們結束了
-Does he know? -Who?
-他知道嗎? -誰?
Joey. You know, he's really nutsy about you.
喬伊.他對你著迷不已
-He is? Why? -You got me.
-是嗎?為什麼? -你可把我問倒了
Right. Excuse me,doesn't this come with a side salad?
沒錯.抱歉,這道菜不是有沙拉嗎?
So are you gonna call him?
你會打電話給他嗎?
-You think he likes me? -No. Joey.
-你認為他喜歡我? -不,是喬伊
Oh! No,he is so smart. He'll figure it out.
不,他很聰明,他會瞭解的
Do you want some chicken?
想吃雞肉?
No. No food with a face.
不.有臉的食物不吃,記得嗎?
-You have not changed. -Yeah,you too.
-你還是沒變 -你也一樣
Thanks. Excuse me? My side salad?
謝謝.抱歉?我的沙拉在哪?
Service here is horrible. Now I know what people mean.
這裡的服務很差.現在我明白為什麼了
Hi! Remember us?
記得我們嗎?
You called about needing a signature on the form?
你剛打電話要我們過來在表格上簽名?
Well,it turns out we need a new one.
但我們需要一張全新的表格
Because,you see, I put the wrong name again.
我又寫錯名字了
-Because -You're that stupid!
-因為… -你就是那麼笨
I am. I'm that stupid.
對,我就是那麼笨
And I'm gonna pay for this with a check.
我要用支票付帳
Your insurance will cover that.
你不知道保險會給付嗎?
I know. I'm just not that bright either.
我知道,只是我也沒那麼聰明
Mon,I'm sorry. I don't think you're like your mother.
摩尼卡,對不起, 我不是真的認為你像你媽媽
That's all right. And I don't think you were selfish.
沒關係.我也不認為你逃婚很自私
Oh,and I'm sorry I said you were a cow.
哦,對不起我說你在中學時是肥豬
That's okay,I was a cow.
沒關係,我就是肥豬
I know. I'm just sorry I said it.
我知道,我只是為我說了這話抱歉
Worst case scenario: Say you never feel like a father.
最糟糕的情況是,你從未感覺像個爸爸
Say your son never feels connected to you as one.
你兒子從未感覺你像個爸爸
Say all of his relationships are affected by this.
他所有的關係全受這個的影響
-Do you have a point? -You know,you'd think I would.
-你這話有沒有重點? -應該有的
What's up with the simian?
這隻猴子到底怎麼了?
-It's just a fur ball. -All right.
-只是毛球 -好吧
-Whose turn? -Yours. I got 43 points for "kidney."
-該誰了? -你.我的kidney得了43分
No,you got zero points for "idney."
不,你沒得分.你拼的是「idney」
I had a "K." Where's my "K"?
不,我有k,我的k在哪兒?
You've got to help me! My monkey swallowed a "K"!
快幫我,我的猴子把k吞了
-Get that animal out! -The animal hospital is across town.
-把你的動物帶走! -不,你不懂.動物醫院離這兒很遠
-What's going on? -Marcel swallowed a Scrabble tile.
-怎麼回事? -馬修吞了一個字母
Excuse me. This hospital is for people!
抱歉,這是為人看病的醫院
He is people! He has a name,okay?
小姐,它是人,他有名字
He watches Jeopardy!,he touches himself when nobody's watching.
他看守「幸運輪」,沒人看時它就摸自己
Please,have a heart.
拜託,發揮你的愛心
-I'll take a look at him. -Thanks.
-我替它看看 -謝謝
-Michael! -Rachel.
-麥克! -瑞秋
-What? -Monica.
-什麼? -莫尼卡
Urs,what are you doing here? I've been trying to call you.
烏蘇拉?你怎麼會在這兒? 我一直打電話找你
Listen....
聽我說
Don't say "listen." I know that "listen." I've said that.
不,別叫我聽.我知道你的意思 我也叫人聽我說過
-I'm sorry. -I don't get it. What happened?
-抱歉 -我不懂,你怎麼了?
What about what you said under the bridge?
你在橋下說過的話呢?
Yeah. You should just forget about what I said under the bridge.
你得忘記我在橋下說過的話
I was talking crazy that night. I was so drunk.
我那一夜喝醉了,胡言亂語
-You don't drink. -That's right,I don't.
-你不喝酒 -沒錯,我不喝酒
-But I was drunk on you. -Oh,Urs
-但我愛你愛得如癡如醉 -烏蘇拉
But it's not gonna work.
我們是沒有結果的
Why? Is it because I'm friends with Phoebe?
為什麼?因為我是菲比的朋友?
Would you stop hanging out with her?
如果是,你願意不和她來往嗎?
No,I couldn't do that.
不行,我辦不到
Then yeah,it's because of Phoebe.
沒錯,就是因為她
So,you know,it's either her or me.
所以,不是她就是我
Then I'm sorry.
那麼我只能說抱歉了
You know,you're gonna be really hard to get over.
忘了你是很難的一件事
I know.
我知道
I don't know whether it's just because we're breaking up or what.
我不知是否因為分手
-But you've never looked so beautiful. -Really?
-你從未這麼漂亮過 -真的?
-Pheebs? -Yeah.
-菲比? -什麼事?
He looks so tiny.
它好小
-We just heard. -ls he okay?
-我剛聽說了 -它沒事吧?
The doctor got the "K" out.
對?醫生已取出k了
He also found an "M" and an "O."
他還發現m和o
We think he was trying to spell out "monkey."
它一定想拼monkey（猴子）
The doctor says he'll be fine. He's just sleeping now.
醫生說它已無大礙,它睡著了
-So,you feel like a dad yet? -No. Why?
-你有當爸爸的感覺沒? -沒有,幹嘛問?
Come on,you came through. You did what you had to do.
拜託,你辦到了.你做了必須做的
-That's very "dad." -Look. He's waking up.
-有爸爸的味道了 -看?它醒了
Hey,fella. How you doing?
老兄?感覺如何?